[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "NNS", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "So Dana, where are we?", "question_tokens": ["So", "Dana", ",", "where", "are", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Well, you know what Piers last night where there were so much hope, so much optimism just because of the fact that the two sides actually sat eyeball to eyeball and talked for an hour and a half.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", "what", "Piers", "last", "night", "where", "there", "were", "so", "much", "hope", ",", "so", "much", "optimism", "just", "because", "of", "the", "fact", "that", "the", "two", "sides", "actually", "sat", "eyeball", "to", "eyeball", "and", "talked", "for", "an", "hour", "and", "a", "half", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Donny & Marie"]}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "So, a little ticky (ph) bird told me early this evening that your first ever concert was would you like to confirm what it was?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "a", "little", "ticky", "(", "ph", ")", "bird", "told", "me", "early", "this", "evening", "that", "your", "first", "ever", "concert", "was", "would", "you", "like", "to", "confirm", "what", "it", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "I would love to, I'm proud of it Donny & Marie.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "love", "to", ",", "I", "'m", "proud", "of", "it", "Donny", "&", "Marie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNPS", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "The worst thing since slavery, I mean when hear this kind of nonsense, what is your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["The", "worst", "thing", "since", "slavery", ",", "I", "mean", "when", "hear", "this", "kind", "of", "nonsense", ",", "what", "is", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Well, I mean I think I have very strong feelings about the value of, of health care reform and what it's going to mean in the lives of millions of Americans it what it means for at people in my home state.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", "I", "think", "I", "have", "very", "strong", "feelings", "about", "the", "value", "of", ",", "of", "health", "care", "reform", "and", "what", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "mean", "in", "the", "lives", "of", "millions", "of", "Americans", "it", "what", "it", "means", "for", "at", "people", "in", "my", "home", "state", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "That's pretty outrage isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "pretty", "outrage", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NASA"], "PERCENT": ["97 percent", "97 percent", "17 percent"]}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "So, how come you've been furloughed which I would imagine would be pretty irritating for anybody but you're a big supporter of the guy that's basically caused it?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "how", "come", "you", "'ve", "been", "furloughed", "which", "I", "would", "imagine", "would", "be", "pretty", "irritating", "for", "anybody", "but", "you", "'re", "a", "big", "supporter", "of", "the", "guy", "that", "'s", "basically", "caused", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Well, I mean, as for why I was furloughed is because 97 percent of NASA has been shutdown and I'm part of that 97 percent of the 17 percent of the government that has been shutdown for this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "as", "for", "why", "I", "was", "furloughed", "is", "because", "97", "percent", "of", "NASA", "has", "been", "shutdown", "and", "I", "'m", "part", "of", "that", "97", "percent", "of", "the", "17", "percent", "of", "the", "government", "that", "has", "been", "shutdown", "for", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Well, you know, I'm a pretty simple guy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "a", "pretty", "simple", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cruz"]}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "That's not good for America or is it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "good", "for", "America", "or", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Well, you know, we used -- laid all that at Senator Cruz's feet, you're laying off a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "used", "--", "laid", "all", "that", "at", "Senator", "Cruz", "'s", "feet", ",", "you", "'re", "laying", "off", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Tell me this, if in a year's time, God forbid, the government remains shutdown and you still haven't been paid any money and NASA has effectively ground to a hold, would you still have such a cheery view of its necessity?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "this", ",", "if", "in", "a", "year", "'s", "time", ",", "God", "forbid", ",", "the", "government", "remains", "shutdown", "and", "you", "still", "have", "n't", "been", "paid", "any", "money", "and", "NASA", "has", "effectively", "ground", "to", "a", "hold", ",", "would", "you", "still", "have", "such", "a", "cheery", "view", "of", "its", "necessity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "Well, I wouldn't say I have a cheery view.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "say", "I", "have", "a", "cheery", "view", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NASA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "The slight segue here, ever since I've got you here as a NASA engineer, have you seen \"Gravity,\" the hit movie yet?", "question_tokens": ["The", "slight", "segue", "here", ",", "ever", "since", "I", "'ve", "got", "you", "here", "as", "a", "NASA", "engineer", ",", "have", "you", "seen", "``", "Gravity", ",", "''", "the", "hit", "movie", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "No, I haven't but my daughter called me last night and said it was just awesome.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "have", "n't", "but", "my", "daughter", "called", "me", "last", "night", "and", "said", "it", "was", "just", "awesome", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NASA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "It's absolutely stunning to watch but I do wonder in what would happen to poor old Sandra Bullock and George Clooney if that was to happen right now with most of NASA furloughed?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "absolutely", "stunning", "to", "watch", "but", "I", "do", "wonder", "in", "what", "would", "happen", "to", "poor", "old", "Sandra", "Bullock", "and", "George", "Clooney", "if", "that", "was", "to", "happen", "right", "now", "with", "most", "of", "NASA", "furloughed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Well, you know, right now of course, I believe that they have the mission controls fully staffed right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "right", "now", "of", "course", ",", "I", "believe", "that", "they", "have", "the", "mission", "controls", "fully", "staffed", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NASA"], "PERSON": ["Sandra Bullock", "George Clooney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "That the government shutdown?", "question_tokens": ["That", "the", "government", "shutdown", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "No, shameful.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "shameful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Your thoughts?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "thoughts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Well, you know, I certainly I'm not comfortable with that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "certainly", "I", "'m", "not", "comfortable", "with", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "And I certainly image you play most cricket, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "certainly", "image", "you", "play", "most", "cricket", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "No, but I hadn't been good at that too.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "I", "had", "n't", "been", "good", "at", "that", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "What did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "You know, I wouldn't call it my life, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "call", "it", "my", "life", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Is America more or less racist since it got its first black President?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "America", "more", "or", "less", "racist", "since", "it", "got", "its", "first", "black", "President", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "You know, I certainly think that some of the issues that Obama has are because he's a man of color.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "certainly", "think", "that", "some", "of", "the", "issues", "that", "Obama", "has", "are", "because", "he", "'s", "a", "man", "of", "color", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "When you see the shutdown of the American government, the squabbling, and the poison between the two sides in Washington, that's as a great American sportsman and a great American, what do you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "the", "shutdown", "of", "the", "American", "government", ",", "the", "squabbling", ",", "and", "the", "poison", "between", "the", "two", "sides", "in", "Washington", ",", "that", "'s", "as", "a", "great", "American", "sportsman", "and", "a", "great", "American", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "I'm disappointed.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "disappointed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "When you walk up the third time, what were you thinking?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "walk", "up", "the", "third", "time", ",", "what", "were", "you", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "My focus was small.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "focus", "was", "small", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "As it's soaring away, then, what are you thinking?", "question_tokens": ["As", "it", "'s", "soaring", "away", ",", "then", ",", "what", "are", "you", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Oh, boy, that's hit good.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "boy", ",", "that", "'s", "hit", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "What if you can relive one moment with your whole career begin, what would it be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "if", "you", "can", "relive", "one", "moment", "with", "your", "whole", "career", "begin", ",", "what", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I'll relive the three homers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "relive", "the", "three", "homers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "How come I know for a fact I'm six years younger than you and you look about 10 years younger than me?", "question_tokens": ["How", "come", "I", "know", "for", "a", "fact", "I", "'m", "six", "years", "younger", "than", "you", "and", "you", "look", "about", "10", "years", "younger", "than", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Wait a minute.", "answer_tokens": ["Wait", "a", "minute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "I'm 29, so how old are you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "29", ",", "so", "how", "old", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", ",", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "What -- I was reading this morning.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "--", "I", "was", "reading", "this", "morning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "When you see 12 year old Marie, as we just saw there, would you change anything, all the swings and things that are arise of outrageous fortune you've been through?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "12", "year", "old", "Marie", ",", "as", "we", "just", "saw", "there", ",", "would", "you", "change", "anything", ",", "all", "the", "swings", "and", "things", "that", "are", "arise", "of", "outrageous", "fortune", "you", "'ve", "been", "through", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "EX", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "You know, I wouldn't change anything.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "change", "anything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "He was fascinating?", "question_tokens": ["He", "was", "fascinating", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "He was.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "So, you might think unusually perceptive of him, but what do you think of what he said there?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "you", "might", "think", "unusually", "perceptive", "of", "him", ",", "but", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "what", "he", "said", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Well, that's how we were raise; we were raise by the same parents.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "how", "we", "were", "raise", ";", "we", "were", "raise", "by", "the", "same", "parents", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "Do, you resent the fact that you missed a conventional childhood or do you celebrate the fact that it was so fabulous?", "question_tokens": ["Do", ",", "you", "resent", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "missed", "a", "conventional", "childhood", "or", "do", "you", "celebrate", "the", "fact", "that", "it", "was", "so", "fabulous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "I love letting my children have as normal life as possible.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "letting", "my", "children", "have", "as", "normal", "life", "as", "possible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Do you twerk?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "twerk", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "I work.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "work", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "And so, do you want to stand her desperation to break out and be something else even it's a bit naughty?", "question_tokens": ["And", "so", ",", "do", "you", "want", "to", "stand", "her", "desperation", "to", "break", "out", "and", "be", "something", "else", "even", "it", "'s", "a", "bit", "naughty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "NN", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "You know, I think everybody has a choice to do what they want with their brand, I don't think she is -- she is stupid, I think she knows exactly what she is doing.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "everybody", "has", "a", "choice", "to", "do", "what", "they", "want", "with", "their", "brand", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "she", "is", "--", "she", "is", "stupid", ",", "I", "think", "she", "knows", "exactly", "what", "she", "is", "doing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "EX", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Because you must have it with Donny all the time the way you navigate through it?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "must", "have", "it", "with", "Donny", "all", "the", "time", "the", "way", "you", "navigate", "through", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Well, you know, there are many right ways, there -- you know, you may think you're right, I may think I am right, we need both be right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "there", "are", "many", "right", "ways", ",", "there", "--", "you", "know", ",", "you", "may", "think", "you", "'re", "right", ",", "I", "may", "think", "I", "am", "right", ",", "we", "need", "both", "be", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "And what did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "I think it was my faith in God that pulled me through it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "was", "my", "faith", "in", "God", "that", "pulled", "me", "through", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131011pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "So in a sense rather than damage of faith it will be, strengthened your faith?", "question_tokens": ["So", "in", "a", "sense", "rather", "than", "damage", "of", "faith", "it", "will", "be", ",", "strengthened", "your", "faith", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]